Oh, that was so close!
Magic of Love!
Granddave!
Hey! I've already hit it!
Goal!
Too fast!
Fast! Fast!
Fast!
Yeah!
Blue!
What? How did you do that?
Oh, my God!
This is really, really bad.
Outro.
That's so hard!
The outro alone is soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo hard!
Microcosmos Macrocosmos
I'm beat!
Yay!
I think I'm better at the outro.
What? That's amazing!
I know it's the real microcosmos.
Okay, okay.
Okay, here we go! Question 6
Alfrasiin.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Pretty for you, not at least a chain
I'd like to make it happen with you.
I'ma be mine
Hear me now It doesn't make any sense
If it's words, I don't need them anymore
It's up now, it's up now
You and me so destined
Now question 6!
Amephrasis Super Intro 9!
Gradation
Yes!
Wait, that's a strong outro.
This song has sign language in the dance.
Blue and blue and orange...
It seems to be a fun song to perform live together.
It seems to be a fun song that you can get excited by doing the choreography together!
Please listen to the song!
What I answered...
Yes, Ayanan answered.
I got it.
Question 7!
Amefurashi super intro 9!
Aah! Oh, no!
What was that?
Tune!
I have no idea. Is it a lucky number?
Yee!
What was that?
I want to be a bachelorette!
Yay!
I don't know what you're talking about.
Here we go.
He's a pussycat!
Onte!
Ponte! What's wrong?
What's wrong with this cat?
If you get puffy, your cheeks will be puffy.
This song is by Mr. Ichikawa,
No, it's not. It is a Yuzuka song.
This song is a Yuzuka song.
It looks like a Yuzu song, but I was told it is a Yuzu Hana song.
It is a Yuzuka song.
It has catchy choreography,
It has some cute lyrics and some lyrics that validate the lyrics,
We sometimes play it as an encore at our live performances,
So please come and see it if you like.
I'm sure you'll be excited when you see it.
Oh my God! I'm so happy!
Question 8: Rain Flash Super Intro 9
Pang!
CUNK
What just now?
What was that?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
We all thought it was an outstart.
I don't know what that was.
Dune.
Oh, my God.
Bloyer mind.
Snap.
Oh, no.
Do you want me to do it again?
Then tell me.
I'm on it.
Amephrasis super intro 9.
Ira.
Disco train.
There you go.
Really?
Olavara Disco Train. This way is fashion day.Olavara Disco Train This Way is Fashion Day
Ring the bell, Motliffen. Motliffen, Motliffen, Motliffen.
Yes, sir.
This is a flower song.
The title of the song is "Disco Train Disco".
Disco dancing in the middle of the song...
It's a very popular and exciting song at live performances.
Please dance with us at the live!
It's a very fun song!
Yes, I'll be there.
That's great Ira!
I'm good at the outro.
But now that the outro's over.
I think I might be good at the next one.
Next up is the speed-up section.
Hey!
Question 9. Amephrasis Super Intro 9.
What?
What is it?
I don't get it.
What?
I don't think so.
Oh, come on.
Can I answer that question one more time?
But you can't take the night off.
I don't know.
Blow Your Mind
No, it's not.
Thank you.
Can I ask you to slow down a little?
Yes.
Question 9: Amephrasis Super Intro 9.
What?
I don't understand.
Slow down again.
Drama.
Hannah, you're back.
Thank you very much.
Let's hear it one more time.
Wait, wait, wait. What?
It's just running a little longer.
Just a little more. Acorns.
Just let it play a little longer until we figure it out.
Amehenasi super intro 9.
I got it!
Grasshopper girl
That's it! Oh my God!
That's for sure!
This is too funny!
You can't blame anyone for this.
Sing it three times faster.
Faster.
I can go faster.
Rock harder.
Faster
Now's the time.
Thank you.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
Cold face.
This song is so bass-heavy.
It looks great live.
I want you to see it live.
It's a really cool song.
The music video is amazing too!
Yes! We do a lot of one-shot shooting.
The music video, the song, etc.
Please come and see us live!
Please do!
Question 10: Rainfall Super Interro Q
Osha-sha-sha!
Fly out! Yes!
I guess we're splitting this one up...
So, before it gets late, Part 1
This is the first part.
Short!
It was pretty short.
It's...
It's a representative song of Amefurashi's recent
This is our 5th anniversary song.
We'll be celebrating our 5th anniversary in November.
And we're trying to spread our wings even more for that.
I don't know how to say it.
I think it's a song that will become a bomb.
I don't know what we are doing now.
I don't know.
It's a Chuckers song.
It's the most commendable song in Amefurashi right now, but
I think it's a song with strong meaning.
Everyone do this together.
Raise the A!
That was easy.
Off-The-Girl was too hard.
I have 4 points.
Okay, 2 points.Okay, two points.
Three points.
One point, please.
Amefrasi Super Intro 9
Start!
Wow! I got it! I got it!
I didn't get it.
Is it heavy?
Sensitive!
That's great. Where is it?
Is it like this?
It sounds like a "hoo".
Where shall we sing?
The quiet beginning is sweet, I know it's sweet
Oh, I'm a sensitive.
Yes, time.
It's cool, it's feminine, it's girlish,
The chorus has a very eccentric choreography with head-swinging,
It is enjoyable to watch and to listen to.
It's a great type of music, so please listen to it if you like.
Yay! We've caught up to No. 1.
That's right.
Question 12: Ougurashi Super Intro Q
Eh, in the hustle and bustle
Oh, yes!
That's not right.
Wait, what is it? I've heard something about this.
I want to hear it again.
May I?
Eye flash, Super Interlocutor Q.
Glow my heart
I thought...
Oh! Yes!
I couldn't remember that one.
It was just something cheerful, wasn't it?
I'm so sorry.
I fucked up so bad.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
The lyrics are totally different.
There's not a single dream in there
I don't have any dreams or hopes
I'm really screwed.
Minus 3 points.
It's a really uplifting song.
This is a very popular song among the fans
It's a song that has a lot of about
It's a song from the early days of AmeFlash.
When we play it live, the crowd goes wild!
It's really cool and
It's a song that fans can enjoy together
It's a song that we play live.
Please come to our live show and enjoy it!
Now that the squall ban has been lifted.
I want you to say the members' names!
Okay, second place and...
Do idols sing a lot?
It's hard to tell.
Oh! I think I get it.
It's not like you understand it when you hear it.
It's the kind of thing you understand when you hear it.
I finally see hope.
I see it now.